Guide to the Harry Gamboa Jr. Papers, 1968-1995
Department of Special Collections
- Series XII: Video Tape Listing
  - Video Tape 8
    - Buzzard Buzzwords, 1994 color/stereo 6 min. Patients are locked out/subjected to toxic measures as mass hysteria ensues. Performed by Del Zamora, Maria Elena Gaitan. Ricardo Gonzalves, Humberto Sandoval, Octavio Tizoc Gaitan-Diaz Diego Gamboa. and Pilbuen Aranas. (Box 15, 8, f)
    - Lost Shadow, 1994 Color/Stereo. 8 min. Older sister (Paulina Sahagun) is tired of baby-sitting her Younger Brother (Moises Corrales) and wants him out of her hair. (Box 15, 8, g)
    - Oasis Erase Us, 1994 Color/Stereo 18 min. Gamblers are lost in a sea of concrete as they place their bets on nothingness. Performed by Linda Gamboa, Humberto Sandoval, Max Benavidez, and Diego Gamboa. (Box 15, 8, h)
    - Asphalt Dialogues, 1994 Color/Stereo 22 min. Anthony C. Sandoval. Cyclona. Willie Garcia, Kara Engel, John Valadez, and Octavio Tizoc Gaitan-Diaz present their perceptions of the present. Title Graphics: Apolina Vargas (Box 15, 8, i)
  - Video Tape 9
    VIDEO TAPE #9 was presented as video element of live performance, ANTIZONA at U.C. Irvine, 1987. The answers given during this tape are in response to questions which were unavailable to the live audience (questions are included in Stanford Collection).
    - MARIA ALAMILLO. 4 min. (Box 15, 9, a)
    - BARBARA CARRASCO. 9 min. (Box 15, 9, b)
    - MARIA ELENA GAITAN. 10 min. (Box 15, 9, c)
    - DANIEL J. MARTINEZ. 9 min. (Flutter/Dropout on MASTER.) (Box 15, 9, d)
    - MAX BENAVIDEZ. 9 min. (Box 15, 9, e)
    - HUMBERTO SANDOVAL. 7 min. (Box 15, 9, f)
  - Video Tape 10
    Video Tape #10 contains the video element of the stories by Gamboa for CLUB LIMBO which was performed live at UC Irvine. Manuscript/audio is included in Stanford Collection.
    - Story #1. 16 min. (Silent) Performed by Ricardo Gonzalves and Diego (Box 15, 10, a)
    - Story #2. 17 min. (Silent) Performed by Barbara Carrasco and Apolina Vargas. (Box 15, 10, b)
    - Story #3. 18 min., (Silent) Performed by Anthony C. Sandoval and Alberto Ybarra. (Box 15, 10, c)
  - Video Tape 11
    - Unedited video of Barbara Carrasco's MFA exhibition reception at CAL ARTS. Various people present: Ramon Favela, Zaragosa Vargas, Diane Gamboa, Zaneta Vargas, Dolores Huerta., Yreina Cervantes, Laura Aguilar, Marcos Sanchez and others. Color/Mono. 14 min. (Box 15, 11, a)
    - Unedited video of Sept 7. 1990 performance of IGNORE THE DENTS at the MILLION DOLLAR THEATRE in downtown L.A. Production by Daniel J.Martinez. Written by Harry Gamboa, Jr. 1 hour, 40 min. (Box 15, 11, b)
  - Video Tape 12
    - Vis a Vid, 1991. 13 min. (Box 15, 12, a)
    - Fire Medicine, 1992. 13 min. (Box 15, 12, b)
    - El Mundo, 1992. 13 min. (Box 15, 12, c)
- Preliminary Collection Guides, outdated
  - Original contents listing. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Contents listing: processing copy. (Box 1, Folder 2)